estore.com.au 2007-12-25

# eStore | Shop Around, Buy From Us!

**eStore.com.au is a wholly-owned subsidiary of City Software Pty Ltd., one of Australia's most trusted online Hardware, Software and Consumables resellers.**

  * Why A Privacy Policy?
  * Getting to Know our Customers
  * Third Party Advertising and Cookies
  * Information Corrections or Changes
  * How We Put Information to Good Use
  * With Whom We May Share Information
  * Our Accountability to You
  * Employee Accountability
  * Notification of Changes

### Why A Privacy Policy? 

City Software respects your individual privacy. This Privacy Policy ('Policy') embodies our commitment to its protection through adherence to fair electronic information practices. This Policy puts you, the individual, in control of how your personal information is processed. You have our promise that we will not electronically process your personal information in any way that is incompatible with this Policy. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact the Web site. 

This Privacy Policy protects your privacy by Informing you about: 

  * The types of personal information City Software collects about you through its Web sites 
  * How it collects that information 
  * The general purposes for which it collects such information 

Assuring you that City Software: 

  * Takes reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. 
  * Implements reasonable policies and procedures to ensure that personal information is kept only for the purposes for which it has been gathered; 
  * Uses reasonable measures to ensure that we have accurately and completely recorded the personal information you have provided; and 
  * Provides you reasonable access to your personal information as well as procedures for correcting or modifying that information where appropriate. 
  * Ensuring accountability to individuals who believe that City Software has not complied with these privacy principles. 

### Getting to Know Our Customers 

City Software is in the business of supplying goods and services to our customers. That requires more than simply offering innovative technical services. It also requires that we understand you, our customer, and your needs. 

We get to know you primarily through the information you provide to us when you contact us to use one or more of our services. The information you provide ranges from basic contact information and payment information. All of the information we request from you when purchasing our goods and/or services is obligatory. When you purchase our goods and/or services, you agree to provide us with complete and current information. 

After you have purchased any of our goods and/or services, we may communicate with you about your account, answer questions you may have about what we provided you, or any other relevant matter. Those communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you with quality service that is responsive to your needs. At the same time, those communications give us helpful insights about you, your preferences and the ways in which we might improve our services. We therefore may maintain this information for future use by City Software. 

The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of that information. We also encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to us (e.g., credit card numbers, account passwords) in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity. 

### Third Party Advertising and Cookies 

We use links to some of our suppliers on our Web site. In the course of providing these links, some of these companies may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser, and may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to their and other web sites in order to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Please also examine the Privacy Policies of these companies. 

### Information Corrections or Changes 

You have the ability to correct or change certain information in our records, such as your address and contact information. The process for changing your information begins at [www.citysoftware.com.au](http://www.citysoftware.com.au/). You may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. If you need assistance or have questions about correcting information, you can contact us via e-mail at [sales@citysoftware.com.au](mailto:sales@citysoftware.com.au).

### How We Put Information to Good Use 

We use any information about you for purposes of monitoring and improving our internal operations, as well as to ensure we:

  * bill you properly, 
  * administer your account in accordance with good and proper accounting practices, and 
  * properly supply the goods and/or services you have requested. 

We also use the information we collect to monitor and improve our internal operations For example; we may correlate Web site traffic information with data about individual users. This data helps us to determine how much our customers use parts of the site, allowing us to enhance it to fit the needs of as many of our customers as possible. We may also break down overall usage statistics according to customers' domain names, browser types, and MIME types by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser). 

Another example of our use of information to enhance the experience of users in our network of sites is our reliance on cookie files. We use cookie files to make it easier for users to access our site or services. A cookie file is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. However, the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above) when you register for City Software services. When you register, we may use a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on our site. 

If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. 

Finally, we use the information we collect to direct important notices and information affecting your account or services, as well as to provide general information that may be of interest to you, including newsletters, surveys, and information about our services or product offerings. You may opt-out of receiving information from us simply by notifying us of your desire in accordance with the opt-out instructions contained in any information message you receive from us. Note, however, that in order to fulfil our service obligations to you, we must continue sending you notices and other important information affecting your account or services. 

### With Whom We May Share Information 

We value you as our own customer and we do not share or disclose any information about you to any external company or organization. The information that you supply to us is used to conduct business transactions with you and to enable us to better meet your needs and requirements. Your information is not sold or given to any other organization. 

When you supply us with a credit card number that is used to make a payment to us we securely transmit this to our bank where the credit card transaction is either accepted or declined by the bank. We do not store your credit card details on any of our sites or systems. The bank stores any necessary details about our transaction/s with you, we do store a payment authorisation reference number associated with your transaction/s. It is not possible for this reference number to be used for any other purpose other than recording the fact that we conducted a credit card transaction with you. 

### Our Accountability to You 

By purchasing our goods and/or services, you obtain the protections of, and consent to the data processing practices described in, this Privacy Policy. When you purchase our services, you also represent to us that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal data you supply to us with regard to:

  * the purposes for which such third party's personal data have been collected, 
  * the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's personal data, 
  * which of the third party's data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary, and 
  * how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them. 

In addition to the privacy protections that we provide, our employees, agents and business partners are independently responsible for ensuring compliance with this Privacy Policy, as described below. 

### Employee Accountability 

Only those City Software employees that have a legitimate business purpose for accessing and handling information obtained by us are given authorization to do so. The unauthorized access or use of such information by a City Software employee is prohibited and constitutes grounds for disciplinary action. 

Additionally, our information management systems are configured in such a way as to block or inhibit employees from accessing information that they have no authority to access. 

### Notification of Changes 

If and when we make any changes to any part of this Privacy Policy we will amend the effective date displayed at the top of this page.

Released December 21st 2001  
_Version 1.0_
